

RAFAEL MORALES

Digital Marketer International MBA in Digital Marketing

PERSONAL HISTORY

I have a total of 7 years of work experience, hands-on experience with touch commerce technology, paid advertising and SEO strategy. More than 3 years of experience in IT industry and 2 years working in digital marketing as freelancer for different companies and leading eCommerce projects.

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- SEO & SEM
- · Web Development & Hosting
- · Analytics & Monitoring
- Remarketing

PLATFORMS AND TOOLS

- Google (Analytics, AdWords, Console)
- WordPress + WooCommerce
- Facebook Ads Manager + Pixel
- Mailchimp + WhatApp Business

CONTACT INFO

WhatsApp: <u>+57 3052661440</u> rafaelmorales112@hotmail.com Current Location: Bogotá, Colombia

Link to My Portfolio

WORK EXPERIENCE

SEO & eCommerce Manager Freelance

Active Visions Group | Jan 2020 - Present

- Creation, management and execution of SEO strategy.
- Manage paid advertising campaigns and social media strategy.
- · Creation of conversion funnels.
- · Design and execution of the content marketing strategy.

Digital Marketing Manager Freelance

Iluminar | 11/2018 - Present

- Increased repeat buying from 10% to 32% by implementing an email retargeting to potential clients and cross-selling strategy.
- Marketing campaigns achieved a ROI of 300%.
- Improved sales funnels and optimized marketing campaigns.

BI Consultant

Zeus Tecnología | Jun 2015 - Oct 2018

- Development of the financial panel to end-user increased the license acquisition of BI department by 25%.
- Elaborated more than 60 personalized ad-hoc reports to customers from different industries: hospitality, retail, manufacturing, health, travel, etc.

EDUCATION

M.Sc. International MBA

ESIC Business & Marketing School - SISU | 2018 - 2020

M.sc. Tax Managemet

Universidad Tecnológica | 2017 - 2018

B.Sc. Business Administrator

Universidad del Norte | 2009 - 2014